Well, everybody, welcome to Amazing Discovery.
好了，大家好，歡迎收看《驚奇發現》。
Oh, oh, it's on again.
啊啊啊又開始了
You guys, could you please not watch this?
各位，能不能別看這個？
Folks, has this ever happened to you?
親們，你們有遇過這樣的情況嗎？
You go to the refrigerator to get a nice glass of milk,
你去冰箱拿一杯好喝的牛奶，
but these darn cartons are so flingin' flangin' hard to open.
但這些該死的紙箱實在太難開啟了。
Well, you said it, Mike.
好吧，你說的是，麥克。
There's gotta be a better way.
一定有更好的辦法。
And there is, Kevin.
還有，凱文。
Could you please turn this off?
你能把這個關掉嗎？
No way, Kevin.
沒辦法，凱文。
There's a revolutionary new product that guarantees
有一個革命性的新產品可以保證
you'll never have to open up milk cartons again.
您再也不用開啟牛奶盒了。
Meet the Milk Master 2000.
來認識一下牛奶大師 2000。
Are you intrigued?
你有興趣嗎？
You're flingin' flangin' right, I am.
你說得對，我也是。
This is the first time he's never used this product before.
這是他第一次使用這個產品。
You're gonna see how easy this is to do.
您將會看到這是多麼容易做到的。
Go ahead.
前進。
This works in any milk carton.
這適用於任何牛奶盒。
Wow, it is easy.
哇，這很容易。
Now I can have milk every day.
現在我可以每天喝牛奶了。
I can't watch this anymore.
我不能再看這個了
Oh, all right, you've suffered enough.
哦，好吧，你已經受夠了。
We'll change it, we'll change it.
我們會改變它，我們會改變它。
How many times has this happened to you?
這種情況在你身上發生過幾次？
There's gotta be a better way.
一定有更好的辦法。
It's a joke you broke.
這是一個你打破的笑話。
Love lost its way.
愛情迷失了方向。
It's like you're always stuck in second gear.
就像你總是被困在二檔一樣。
When it hasn't been your day, your week, your month,
當這不是你的一天、你的一週、你的一個月時，
or even your year.
甚至是你的年份。
But I'll be there for you.
但我會在你身邊。
When the rain starts to pour.
當雨開始傾盆而下。
I'll be there for you.
我會在那等你。
Like I've been there before.
就像我以前去過那裡一樣。
I'll be there for you.
我會在那等你。
Because you're there for me too
因為你也在我身邊
It's official, there are no good movies.
這是官方的，沒有好電影。
So let's go to a bad one and make out.
那我們就來看看壞事吧。
Ha ha ha ha!
哈哈哈哈！
Perhaps you would like me to turn like this, so you can bunny bump against my back.
也許你希望我像這樣轉動，這樣你就可以兔子撞到我的背上。
Hey!
嘿！
Hey man! What's up?
嘿夥計！這是怎麼回事？
Maybe you can tell me.
也許你可以告訴我。
My agent would like to know why I didn't show up at the audition I didn't know I had today.
我的經紀人想知道為什麼我沒有出現在我今天不知道的試鏡中。
The first good thing she gets me in weeks.
這是她幾週來帶給我的第一件好事。
How could you not give me the message?
你怎麼能不給我訊息呢？
I'll tell you, I do enjoy guilt.
我告訴你，我確實喜歡內疚。
But, uh, it wasn't me.
但是，呃，那不是我。
Yes it was, it was him, uh-huh.
是的，就是他，嗯哼。
Okay, it was me.
好吧，是我。
How was it you?
你怎麼樣？
Well, it was just, it was all so crazy, you know?
好吧，這一切都太瘋狂了，你知道嗎？
I mean, Chandler was in the closet counting to ten and he was up to seven
我的意思是，錢德勒在衣櫃裡數到十，而他數到了七
and I hadn't found a place to hide yet.
而我還沒找到躲藏的地方。
I, I meant to tell you and I wrote it all down on my hand, see? All of it.
我，我本來想告訴你的，我都寫在手上了，懂嗎？所有這一切。
Yep, that's my audition.
是的，這就是我的試鏡。
See? Now this is why I keep notepads everywhere.
看？這就是為什麼我到處放記事本的原因。
Yep, and that's why we don't invite you to play.
是的，這就是我們不邀請你玩的原因。
What is the great tragedy here? You go get yourself another appointment.
這裡最大的悲劇是什麼？你去給自己另一個約會。
Well, Estelle tried, you know?
嗯，埃斯特爾嘗試過，你知道嗎？
The casting director told her I missed my chance.
選角導演告訴她我錯過了機會。
Well, that is unfair.
嗯，這是不公平的。
I'll call her, I'll tell her it was totally my fault.
我會打電話給她，我會告訴她這完全是我的錯。
Sheesh, you can't do that. The casting director doesn't talk to friends, she only talks to agents.
希什，你不能這麼做。選角導演不與朋友交談，她只與經紀人交談。
What a sad little life she must lead.
她必須過著多麼悲傷的小生活。
Okay, ooh.
好吧，哦。
What are you doing? What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？你在幹什麼？
No, no, no, I know, I know, ooh.
不不不，我知道，我知道，哦。
Hi, this is Caitlin from Phoebe Buffay's office.
大家好，我是菲比·布菲辦公室的凱特琳。
Um, is, um, Anne there? For Phoebe?
嗯，嗯，安妮在嗎？為了菲比？
She'll know what it's about.
她會知道這是關於什麼的。
Hang on, hang on for a second.
等一下，等一下。
Anne, hot.
安妮，熱。
Listen, we've got a problem with Joey Tribbiani.
聽著，我們和喬伊·崔比亞尼之間有一個問題。
Apparently he missed his audition.
顯然他錯過了試鏡。
Who did you speak to in my office?
你在我辦公室和誰說話？
Estelle? No, I don't know what I'm going to do with her.
埃斯特爾？不，我不知道我要對她做什麼。
No, alright, so your husband leaves you and then burns down the apartment.
不，好吧，所以你的丈夫離開了你，然後燒毀了公寓。
The world does not stop.
世界並沒有停止。
Is anybody else scared?
還有人害怕嗎？
Right, well look, if Joey loses this audition, then that is it for Estelle.
好吧，好吧，如果喬伊輸掉了這次試鏡，那麼艾斯特爾也就結束了。
I don't care.
我不在乎。
Anne, you are a doll.
安妮，你是個洋娃娃。
What time can you see him?
你什麼時候能見到他？
I need a pad.
我需要一個墊子。
Get the woman a pad, get the woman a pad.
給女人一個護墊，給女人一個護墊。
A pad, a pad.
一個墊子，一個墊子。
Oh, now you want a pad.
哦，現在你想要一個墊子。
Huh, well that's funny.
嗯，這很有趣。
Ugly naked guy's still naked, but his dog's wearing a sweater.
醜陋的裸體傢伙仍然赤身裸體，但他的狗穿著一件毛衣。
Hey.
嘿。
Here's my boy.
這是我的男孩。
And here's his Barbie.
這是他的芭比娃娃。
What's, uh, what's my boy doing with the Barbie?
呃，我的兒子在拿芭比娃娃做什麼？
He picked it out at the toy store himself.
他自己在玩具店挑選的。
He loves it.
他喜歡它。
He carries it everywhere, it's like a security blanket.
他到處都帶著它，它就像一條安全毯。
But with ski boots and a kicky beret.
但搭配滑雪靴和漂亮的貝雷帽。
Yeah, it's, it's, it's cute.
是的，這，這，這很可愛。
Why, why, why does he have it again?
為什麼，為什麼，為什麼他又擁有了？
So it's got a doll, so what?
所以它有一個娃娃，那又怎樣？
Unless you're afraid he's gonna grow up to be in show business.
除非你擔心他長大後會進入演藝界。
That's what it had to do with the fact that he's been raised by two women, wouldn't it?
這就是因為他是由兩個女人撫養長大的，不是嗎？
You know what, it's fine.
你知道嗎，沒關係。
If you're okay with the Barbie thing, so am I.
如果你對芭比娃娃感到滿意，我也同意。
Give daddy the Barbie.
把芭比娃娃送給爸爸。
Give me the Barbie.
把芭比娃娃給我。
Okay, how about, don't you want to play with a momster truck?
好吧，怎麼樣，你不想和媽媽卡車一起玩嗎？
Okay, how about a dino soldier?
好吧，恐龍士兵怎麼樣？
Ross, you are so pathetic.
羅斯，你真是太可憐了。
Why can't your son just play with his doll?
為什麼你的兒子不能玩他的洋娃娃？
I gotta go to work.
我得去上班了。
Has anybody seen my left boob?
有人看到我的左胸了嗎？
I love that movie.
我喜歡那部電影。
It is? Joey, what are you doing?
這是？喬伊，你在做什麼？
I'm sorry, it just felt nice.
抱歉，只是感覺很好。
Joey, Joey, answer the phone.
喬伊，喬伊，接電話。
Hey, I only got one good arm, you know, you should be doing stuff for me.
嘿，我只有一隻好手臂，你知道，你應該為我做點什麼。
Go get me a sweater.
去買一件毛衣給我。
Just do it, okay? It's Janice, and if I get it, I'm gonna have to see her tonight.
就做吧，好嗎？我是珍妮絲，如果我找到了，我今晚就得去見她。
Oh, that's great. I'm gonna have to see her tonight.
哦，那太好了。今晚我要去見她。
What's the big deal? Why don't you want to see Janice?
有什麼大不了的？為什麼不想見珍妮絲？
Okay, last night at dinner, when the meals came,
好吧 昨晚吃飯的時候 飯菜上來的時候
she put half her chicken piccata on my plate, and then she took all my tomatoes.
她把一半的雞肉皮卡塔放在我的盤子裡，然後她拿走了我所有的番茄。
That's bad because you hate chicken piccata?
這很糟糕，因為你討厭雞肉皮卡塔？
No.
不。
You didn't want to share your tomatoes.
你不想分享你的西紅柿。
Tomatoes are very important to you.
西紅柿對你來說非常重要。
No, it's like all of a sudden we were this couple, okay?
不，就像突然間我們就成為了這對情侶，好嗎？
And this alarm started going off in my head, you know?
這個警報開始在我的腦海中響起，你知道嗎？
Run for your life! Get out of the building!
為你的生命奔跑！離開大樓！
Men are unbelievable.
男人是難以置信的。
Janice just thought she was giving you chicken.
珍妮絲只是以為她在給你雞肉。
She didn't think she was giving you scary chicken.
她不認為她給了你可怕的雞肉。
What is it with you people?
你們怎麼了？
I mean, the minute you start to feel something, you have to run away?
我是說，一旦你開始感覺到什麼，就必須逃跑？
I know, that...
我知道，那...
That's why I don't want to go tonight.
這就是為什麼我今晚不想去。
I'm afraid I'm gonna say something stupid.
我怕我會說些蠢話。
Oh, you mean like that guy thing where you act all mean and distant
哦，你的意思是像那個傢伙那樣，你表現得很卑鄙和疏遠
until you get us to break up with you?
直到你讓我們跟你分手？
Hey, you know about that?
嘿，你知道嗎？
What do I do? I want to get past this.
我該怎麼辦？我想克服這個。
I don't want to be afraid of the commitment thing.
我不想害怕承諾的事。
I want to go through the tunnel to the other side.
我想穿過隧道到另一邊。
Where there's no fear of commitment.
那裡不用擔心承諾。
Do we have any...
我們有沒有什麼...
Do we have any thoughts here?
說到這裡我們有什麼想法嗎？
Well, I've never been through the tunnel myself
好吧，我自己從來沒有穿過隧道
because, as I understand it, you're not allowed to go through
因為據我瞭解，你不被允許透過
with more than one girl in the car, right?
車上不只一個女孩，對嗎？
But it seems to me it's pretty much like anything else, you know?
但在我看來，這和其他事情很相似，你知道嗎？
Face your fear.
面對你的恐懼。
You have a fear of heights?
你有懼高症嗎？
You go to the top of the building.
你走到建築物的頂部。
You're afraid of bugs?
你害怕蟲子嗎？
Get a bug.
獲取錯誤。
Right?
正確的？
In this case, you have a fear of commitment.
在這種情況下，你害怕承諾。
So I say you go in there
所以我說你進去吧
and you be the most committed guy there ever was.
你將成為有史以來最忠誠的人。
Amazingly, that makes sense.
令人驚訝的是，這是有道理的。
Do you think?
你認為嗎？
Oh, yeah. Go for it, man.
哦，是的。加油吧，老兄。
Jump off the high dive.
從高處跳下。
Stare down the barrel of the gun.
盯著槍管。
Pee into the wind.
向風撒尿。
Yeah, Joe, I assure you, if I'm staring down the barrel of a gun,
是的，喬，我向你保證，如果我盯著槍管，
I'm gonna be pretty much peeing every which way.
我幾乎會到處撒尿。
You guys, listen to this and tell me what you think, okay?
你們，聽聽這個，然後告訴我你們的想法，好嗎？
That's interesting.
那很有意思。
Oh, because it's a beeper.
哦，因為它是一個蜂鳴器。
Oh, it's your audition from this morning.
哦，這是你今天早上的試鏡。
Can I use the phone again?
我可以再使用手機嗎？
Sure, babes. You know, that's what they're for.
當然，寶貝們。你知道，這就是他們的目的。
Emergencies and pretend agents.
緊急情況和假裝特工。
Come on, baby, come on.
來吧，寶貝，來吧。
Hi, I have Phoebe Buffay returning a page.
您好，我請菲比·布菲回一頁。
Okay, well, she's in her car.
好吧，她在車上。
I'll have to patch you through.
我得給你打補丁。
Very nice touch.
非常好的觸感。
Okay, go ahead.
好的，繼續吧。
Oh, oh, um...
哦，哦，嗯...
Hi, Annie.
嗨，安妮。
Fantastic. You got it.
極好的。你明白了。
Oh, okay, um...
哦，好吧，嗯...
Will he work for scale, you ask me?
你問我，他會努力擴大規模嗎？
Well, I don't know about that.
嗯，我對此一無所知。
Except that I do and he will.
只不過我會這麼做，他也會這麼做。
Great. Oh, you are such a sweetheart.
偉大的。哦，你真是個甜心。
I would love to have lunch with you.
我很想和你一起吃午餐。
How about we have lunch
我們吃午餐怎麼樣
next?
下一個？
Oop, went through a tunnel.
哎呀，穿過隧道了。
Unbelievable.
難以置信。
Thank you so much.
太感謝了。
It was really fun.
真的很有趣。
I mean, I've never talked on a car phone before.
我的意思是，我以前從未用車載電話通話過。
That was so amazing.
那真是太神奇了。
Can you do me this huge favor?
你能幫我這個大忙嗎？
See, there's this one other audition
看，還有另一場試鏡
that I really, really want and Estelle couldn't get me in.
我真的非常想要，但埃斯特爾無法讓我進去。
I don't know. I mean, it was fun one time, but...
我不知道。我的意思是，有一次很有趣，但是...
Come on, please. It would just be this one more.
來吧，請。就只剩下這個了。
Well, actually, it's two.
嗯，實際上，是兩個。
Two?
二？
Yeah.
是的。
Well, really, it's three.
嗯，確實是三個。
You're so good at it.
你太擅長了。
I love you.
我愛你。
Okay, I'll do it. But just these three, right?
好的，我會做的。但只有這三個，對嗎？
No, it's four.
不，是四個。
So how come you wanted to eat in tonight?
那你今晚怎麼想來吃飯？
Because I wanted to
因為我想
give you this.
給你這個。
Oh, are you a puppy?
哦，你是小狗嗎？
Contact paper.
接觸紙。
You never really know what to say
你永遠不知道該說什麼
when someone you're sleeping with gives you contact paper.
當和你一起睡的人給你接觸紙。
Wait, there's more.
等等，還有更多。
See, the contact paper is to go in
看，接觸紙要進去
your brand new drawer.
你全新的抽屜。
See, the drawer actually goes
瞧，抽屜真的動了
in my dresser.
在我的梳妝臺裡。
Oh, you didn't have to do this.
哦，你不必這樣做。
Yes, I did.
是的，我做到了。
Because you're my girlfriend
因為你是我女朋友
and that's what girlfriends should get.
這就是女朋友該得到的。
Oh, well, I gotta
哦，好吧，我得
buy a vowel.
買一個母音。
Because, oh,
因為，哦，
my God!
我的上帝！
Mom, who would've thought
媽媽誰能想到
that someday Chandler Bing
有一天錢德勒賓
would buy me a drawer?
會買一個抽屜給我嗎？
Not me.
不是我。
But that's what's happened.
但事實就是這樣。
And, uh, and there's more.
而且，呃，還有更多。
We should take a trip.
我們應該去旅行。
We should?
我們應該？
Yep, we're a couple and that's, uh,
是的，我們是情侶，那是，呃，
what couples do.
情侶做什麼。
And I wanna meet your parents.
我想見見你的父母。
We should take a trip with your parents.
我們應該和你父母一起去旅行。
I don't think we need to
我認為我們不需要
because you're tripping me out right now.
因為你現在正在絆倒我。
Are you okay?
你還好嗎？
No, I am. I actually am.
不，我是。我確實是。
I mean, this is amazing.
我的意思是，這太棒了。
My entire life, I have feared
我一生都在害怕
this place.
這個地方。
And now that I'm here, it's like,
現在我在這裡，就像，
what was the big deal?
有什麼大不了的？
I mean, I could probably say,
我的意思是，我可能會說，
let's move in together and I'd be okay.
我們搬到一起住吧，我就沒事了。
You probably want us to move in together?
你可能希望我們搬到一起住？
It doesn't scare me.
這並沒有嚇到我。
Yeah, well, it scares me.
是的，好吧，這讓我害怕。
I mean, I'm not even divorced yet.
我的意思是，我還沒有離婚。
Chandler, you know, you just invited me over here
錢德勒，你知道，你剛剛邀請我來這裡
for pasta and all of a sudden you're, like,
吃義大利麵，突然間你就像，
talking about moving in together
談論搬到一起住
and I wasn't even that hungry.
我甚至沒那麼餓。
But it's getting really late
但時間真的已經很晚了
and I should just, um...
我應該，嗯...
Oh, no, don't go! I've scared you.
哦，不，別走！我嚇到你了。
I've said too much.
我已經說太多了。
I'm hopeless and awkward and desperate for love.
我對愛情感到絕望、尷尬和絕望。
Hey, Janice, it's me.
嘿，珍妮絲，是我。
Um, yeah,
嗯，是的，
I just wanted to apologize in advance
我只是想提前道歉
for having chased you down the street.
因為在街上追你。
There you go, honey.
就這樣吧，親愛的。
This will help.
這會有幫助。
So, I finally catch up to her
所以我終於追上了她
and she says this relationship's going too fast
她說這段關係進展得太快了
and we have to slow down.
我們必須放慢速度。
Ugh, that is never good.
呃，那永遠都不好。
And I got all...
而我得到了所有...
needy and clingy.
需要幫助並且黏人。
You didn't beg, did you?
你沒有乞求吧？
I said please.
我說請。
Well, was it please with one E
嗯，有一個 E 嗎？
in the middle of it or lots of Es?
中間還是很多 E？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Oh, dear Lord, I begged.
哦，親愛的主，我懇求道。
Oh, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
哦，等一下，等一下，等一下。
Maybe it's not so bad. How did you leave it?
也許情況並沒有那麼糟。你是怎麼離開的？
She said she'd call me.
她說她會打電話給我。
Oh!
哦！
Oh, God.
哦，上帝。
Welcome to our side of the tunnel.
歡迎來到我們這邊的隧道。
This ice cream tastes like crap, by the way.
順便說一句，這個冰淇淋嘗起來像垃圾。
Yeah, well, that's that low-cal
是啊，就是這麼低熱量
non-dairy soy milk junk.
非乳製品豆漿垃圾。
We sort of... We saved the real stuff
我們有點...我們儲存了真實的東西
for the truly terminal cases.
對於真正的末期病例。
You know, when you start getting screwed over all the time,
你知道，當你開始一直被搞砸時，
you gotta switch to low-fat.
你必須改吃低脂食物。
Yeah, you do.
是的，你知道。
You don't think I'm terminal?
你不認為我是終結者嗎？
No, not at all.
不，一點也不。
You're not terminal. You just...
你不是終端。你只是...
We just need some damage control.
我們只需要一些損害控制。
Okay, okay. So should I call her?
好吧，好吧。那我該打給她嗎？
No!
不！
Very critical time right now.
現在非常關鍵的時刻。
If you feel yourself reaching for that phone,
如果你覺得自己伸手去拿那支手機，
you go shoe shopping. You get your butt in a bubble bath.
你去買鞋。你把屁股泡在泡泡浴裡。
If you want her back,
如果你想讓她回來
you have got to start acting aloof.
你必須開始表現得冷漠。
Aloof?
超然？
She needs to know that you're not needy.
她需要知道你並不需要幫助。
Right. So what you have to do is
正確的。所以你要做的是
you have to accidentally run into her
你必須不小心碰到她
on purpose
故意的
and then act aloof.
然後表現得冷漠。
And then I'll be okay?
然後我就沒事了？
Yeah, I think so.
是的，我想是的。
So I'm not gonna lose her?
那我就不會失去她了？
Oh, honey,
哦，親愛的，
you're not a total loser.
你並不是一個徹頭徹尾的失敗者。
I said, so I'm not gonna lose her?
我說，那我就不會失去她了？
Oh.
哦。
Guess who's here?
猜猜誰在這裡？
It's the toughest guy
這是最難纏的人
in Toyland, Ben.
在玩具樂園，本.
Real American hero.
真正的美國英雄。
I'm G.I. Joe.
我是大兵。喬.
Drop the bar. Drop the bar.
放下吧檯。放下吧檯。
G.I. Joe?
特種兵喬？
You really think he's gonna fall for that?
你真的認為他會因此而墮落嗎？
G.I. Joe?
特種兵喬？
Cool. Can I play?
涼爽的。我可以玩嗎？
Look, Ben.
看，本。
It's a toy that protects U.S. oil interests overseas.
這是一個保護美國海外石油利益的玩具。
Go, Joe!
走吧，喬！
Phoebe, there you are.
菲比，你來了。
No, it's not. Sorry.
不，不是。對不起。
Phoebe, wait. Wait, Phoebe.
菲比，等等。等等，菲比。
Oh, Joey. Oh, okay.
哦，喬伊。哦好的。
See, I didn't recognize you
你看，我沒認出你來
in those pants.
在那條褲子裡。
Listen, that TV movie
聽著，那部電視電影
I went in for, did you hear anything?
我進去了，你聽到什麼了嗎？
I think I got a shot at it.
我想我有機會。
Yes, they called. You didn't get it.
是的，他們打電話了。你沒明白。
Okay, I mean,
好吧，我的意思是，
you didn't get it. I'm sorry.
你沒明白。對不起。
That's okay.
沒關係。
These things happen.
這些事情都會發生。
But they shouldn't
但他們不應該
happen. You know what?
發生。你知道嗎？
You're in a terrible, terrible business.
你的生意非常糟糕。
Oh, God, I don't want
哦，上帝，我不想
to be the person who makes your face look like that.
成為那個讓你的臉看起來像那樣的人。
I'm okay.
我沒事。
See?
看？
And you're sad and creepy.
而你又悲傷又令人毛骨悚然。
You know what?
你知道嗎？
I'm sorry. I quit, okay?
對不起。我放棄了，好嗎？
No. No, no, you can't quit.
不，不，不，你不能放棄。
You're the best agent I ever had.
你是我遇到過的最好的經紀人。
Look, Phoebs, rejection is part
瞧，菲布斯，拒絕也是一部分
of being an actor. You can't take it personal.
作為一名演員。你不能把它視為針對個人的。
Not personal? Really?
不是個人的？真的嗎？
They said they'd never met an Italian actor
他們說他們從未見過義大利演員
with a worse Italian accent.
帶有更糟糕的義大利口音。
They actually said that?
他們居然這麼說？
Yeah. Oh, God, there's that face again.
是的。天啊，那張臉又出現了。
See? I can't do this job.
看？我做不了這個工作。
No, no, see, this is why you have to do this job.
不，不，看，這就是你必須做這份工作的原因。
Agents always lie.
經紀人總是說謊。
You know, Estelle just said stuff like,
你知道，艾斯特爾剛剛說過這樣的話，
they went another way.
他們走了另一條路。
But this, I can use this.
不過這個，我可以用這個。
I kind of work on a Yu Akasente.
我從事 Yu Akasete 的工作。
Yeah, okay, no,
是啊，好吧，不，
if it helps you, okay, yeah.
如果對你有幫助的話，好的，好的。
You'll never get me, Joe!
你永遠抓不到我，喬！
Chandler.
錢德勒。
Hello, Janice.
你好，賈妮絲。
What are you doing here?
你在這裡做什麼？
Just a bit of shopping.
只是購物一點。
How have you been?
你最近怎麼樣？
Are you being British?
你是英國人嗎？
No.
不。
Not anymore.
不再。
Why are you shopping here?
為什麼在這裡購物？
You don't live in this neighborhood.
你不住在這個街區。
Were you here waiting for me?
你在這兒等我嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
I'm just, you know,
我只是，你知道，
picking up some things for a party.
為聚會挑選一些東西。
Barley?
大麥？
What kind of a party serves barley?
什麼樣的聚會供應大麥？
Well, I'm sorry if my friends
好吧，我很抱歉如果我的朋友們
aren't as sophisticated as yours.
沒有你的那麼複雜。
Where is this party?
這個聚會在哪裡？
Here in Chelsea.
在切爾西這裡。
Whose party is it?
這是誰的政黨？
A woman's.
一個女人的。
What woman?
什麼女人？
Chelsea.
切爾西。
Okay, you know, one of two things
好吧，你知道，兩件事之一
is happening here.
正在這裡發生。
Either you're seeing somebody behind my back,
要嘛你在背後看到有人
which would make you the biggest jerk on the planet,
這會讓你成為地球上最大的混蛋
or else you're pretending that you're seeing
否則你會假裝你看到了
somebody, which just makes you so pathetic
某人，這讓你變得如此可悲
I could just start crying right here in the cereal aisle.
我簡直可以在麥片貨架上哭了。
So, like, which of these two guys
所以，就像，這兩個人中的哪一個
do you want to be?
你想成為嗎？
Couldn't I be that guy?
我就不能是那個人嗎？
Okay, so we got some more good rejections.
好吧，我們得到了一些更好的拒絕。
Lots of stuff to work on.
有很多事情要做。
Okay, shoot.
好吧，射擊。
Okay, um, oh, the zoo commercial.
好吧，嗯，哦，動物園廣告。
I didn't get it?
我沒聽懂？
No, they said that you weren't believable
不，他們說你不可信
as a human being.
作為一個人。
Work on that.
努力吧。
What else?
還有什麼？
The off-Broadway play people said that you were pretty, but dumb.
外百老匯的戲劇人說你很漂亮，但很笨。
Oh.
哦。
Oh, no, wait, I'm sorry, that's pretty dumb.
哦，不，等等，對不起，這太愚蠢了。
It's okay, no, no, no.
沒關係，不，不，不。
Really.
真的。
Look, um, I really appreciate this, Pheebs,
聽著，嗯，我真的很感激，Pheebs，
but I think I'm gonna
但我想我會
have to go back to Estelle.
必須回到埃斯特爾身邊。
Oh.
哦。
Yeah, well, don't get me wrong, you're a better agent than she is,
是的，好吧，別誤會我的意思，你是比她更好的特工，
but at least with her,
但至少和她在一起，
I don't want to blow my pretty dumb brains out.
我不想把我那愚蠢的腦袋炸出來。
Yeah, no, I understand.
是的，不，我明白。
You do? Thanks.
你做？謝謝。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
What? Wait a minute.
什麼？等一下。
Did you just make all that stuff up to get out of being my agent?
你編造這些事是為了逃避當我的經紀人嗎？
Oh, it caught me.
哦，它抓住了我。
I am so busted.
我真是太崩潰了。
That's what I suspect.
這就是我懷疑的。
And then I just, you know,
然後我就，你知道，
threw the bag of barley at her
把一袋大麥丟給她
and ran out of the store.
並跑出了商店。
My God, Chandler,
天哪，錢德勒，
we said be aloof, not a doof.
我們說要冷漠，不要呆。
I've actually ruined this,
我真的毀了這個
haven't I?
我不是嗎？
It's time for the good ice cream now, right?
現在是吃美味冰淇淋的時候了，對吧？
It's time.
是時候了。
Yeah, it is.
是的，確實如此。
Everything's gonna be okay.
一切都會好起來的。
You know why?
你知道為什麼嗎？
Because you've got 65 grams of fat coming your way.
因為你已經攝取了 65 克脂肪。
Hello?
你好？
Hi, Janice.
嗨，賈妮絲。
Can you hold on for a second?
你能堅持一下嗎？
Okay. Okay.
好的。好的。
What do I do?
我該怎麼辦？
I don't know, this is totally unprecedented.
我不知道，這完全是史無前例的。
If we ever did what you did,
如果我們曾經做過你做過的事
a man would never call.
一個男人永遠不會打電話來。
Okay, you know what? I got it.
好吧，你知道嗎？我得到了它。
Pretend that you just woke up, okay?
假裝你剛醒來，好嗎？
Then I'll throw her off. Be sleepy.
那我就把她丟了。困了。
Yes, and grumpy.
是的，而且脾氣暴躁。
Stop naming dwarves.
別再給矮人取名字了。
Hello, Janice.
你好，賈妮絲。
Hi. I'm so glad that you called.
你好。我很高興你打電話來。
I know I've been acting really weird
我知道我一直表現得很奇怪
lately, and
最近，以及
it's just
這只是
because I'm crazy about you,
因為我為你瘋狂
and
和
I just
我只是
got stupid and
變得愚蠢並且
scared and
害怕和
stupid a couple more times.
多傻幾次。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
Really?
真的嗎？
He's so lucky.
他真幸運。
If Janice were a guy,
如果珍妮絲是個男人
she'd be sleeping with somebody else by now.
她現在已經和別人一起睡了。
I love you, too.
我也愛你。
So unfair.
太不公平了。
G.I. Joe. G.I. Joe.
特種兵喬.特種兵喬.
I don't know what to tell you guys.
我不知道該告訴你們什麼。
That's the doll he chose.
這就是他選的娃娃。
What'd you do? Dip it in sugar?
你做了什麼？沾點糖嗎？
G.I. Joe's in.
特種兵喬進來了。
Barbie's out.
芭比出來了
And if you guys can't deal with it,
如果你們無法應付的話
that's just your too bad.
那隻是你太糟糕了。
What are you being
你是什​​麼身份
such a weenie for?
這樣的小寶貝是為了什麼？
Somebody's a Barbie, big deal.
有人是芭比娃娃，有什麼大不了的。
You used to dress up like a woman.
你以前打扮得像個女人。
What?
什麼？
We used to dress up in mom's clothes all the time.
我們以前總是穿著媽媽的衣服。
What are you talking about?
你在說什麼？
The big hat, the pearls,
大帽子，珍珠，
the little pink handbag.
粉紅色小手提包。
Okay. You are totally making this up.
好的。這完全是你編造的。
How can you not remember?
怎麼會不記得呢？
You made us call you B.
你讓我們叫你B。
Oh, God.
哦，上帝。
I've literally
我確實
never been this happy.
從來沒有這麼開心過。
Wasn't there a little song?
不是有一首小歌嗎？
Oh, please, God, let there be a song.
噢，上帝啊，請賜予一首歌吧。
There was no song.
沒有歌。
I am B.
我是B。
I drink tea.
我喝茶。
Won't you?
你不會嗎？
Won't you dance around with me?
你不跟我一起跳舞嗎？
I am
我是
B.
I drink tea.
我喝茶。
Won't you
你不會嗎
dance around
跳舞
with...
與...
with me?
與我一起？